[Music]
[Applause]
for all we know she's been held against
her will in the Attic for six years not
such a funny clip anymore is it did you
saw her she fell did you saw how she
fell did you hear - how you speak
English you close your eyes it sounds
pretty hot
and stop crying and replace your divot
she may never waddle again
[Music]
well they time this movie perfectly
earthquakes have been trending for like
a month now they're so hot
[Music]
[Applause]
aim for the jacuzzi at Mass
mouth-breather jumps off the roofs of
hotels and apartment complexes all over
the OSI technically he's not diving so
it is allowed
the heavy breathing is getting me all
wooded up wouldn't kill him to mix it up
a little and throw in a gainer his
breathing would lead me to believe this
one has higher stakes you better pray
nobody parked their submarine down there
[Applause]
do the golden gate next the problem is
showing these videos on TV is now
there's gonna be copycat jumpers like
the one that broke into our office the
other day
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'll tell you what our office needs a
pool at this point it's more dangerous
to own a GoPro than a gun now everything
here is cold gray and depressing so
we're either in Russia or Jersey for
this week's breakdown
no need for lighter fluid when there's
cheap vodka seeping out of all your
pores
that's the warmers anyone has ever been
in that godforsaken hellhole
I'm sure baggy sweatpants and a t-shirt
work the same as a wingsuit you're not
supposed to take the elevator in the
event of a fire you jump to if you're
hot high school sweetheart
was just sold to some 50-something
divorcee in Dayton Ohio if you're dumb
enough to try this at home please don't
you want my key demo and I need each and
every one of you to keep watching it all
right from this angle you can really see
how stupid he is
[Music]
your legs are very badly burned but
luckily your neck is broken so you can't
feel it he's being arrested oh I forgot
it's illegal to be flamin in Russia
I'm just glad commies Got Talent there's
a hundred times better than seeing a
six-year-old American play the kazoo and
for that we thank you
you